<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>BlueyFest</title><link>https://blueyfest.dog/</link><description>Recent content on BlueyFest</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://blueyfest.dog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title/><link>https://blueyfest.dog/bit-rate/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blueyfest.dog/bit-rate/</guid><description/></item><item><title/><link>https://blueyfest.dog/discord/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blueyfest.dog/discord/</guid><description/></item><item><title/><link>https://blueyfest.dog/ponytown/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blueyfest.dog/ponytown/</guid><description/></item><item><title>About</title><link>https://blueyfest.dog/about/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blueyfest.dog/about/</guid><description>What is PonyFest? Ponyfest is an annual online convention for the My Little Pony (MLP) community. The convention started in 2020 and has since become a well-known event in the MLP community.
One of the key benefits of Ponyfest is that it&amp;rsquo;s entirely online, which means that attendees from all over the world can participate without worrying about travel costs or accommodation, allowing the event to attract a diverse range of attendees from all walks of life.</description></item><item><title>Charity Concert T-Shirt</title><link>https://blueyfest.dog/shirt/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blueyfest.dog/shirt/</guid><description>Charity T-Shirt All money raised from this shirt not used for production, handling and shipping goes directly to Guide Dogs For America: https://www.guidedogsofamerica.org/
Guide Dogs For America is one of the major organizations in the United States specialized in raising, training and connecting guide dogs with people in need. Through their training and placement programmes, based on the Assistance Dogs International standard, Guide Dogs For America provides service dogs for people with visual impairments, for veterans, for autistic youth as well as care facilities.</description></item><item><title>Faqs</title><link>https://blueyfest.dog/faqs/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blueyfest.dog/faqs/</guid><description>FAQS With the recent influx of questions, we created this FAQ section for common answers.
Q: What kind of convention is BlueyFest Online?
A: BlueyFest is an online convention accessible to anyone and is rated as a PG convention and suitable for all ages.
Q: Is BlueyFest Online appropriate for children?
A: Yes, BlueyFest Online is appropriate for children. The event is designed to be family-friendly and is suitable for attendees of all ages.</description></item><item><title>Schedule</title><link>https://blueyfest.dog/schedule/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blueyfest.dog/schedule/</guid><description> Schedule Schedule Loading...</description></item><item><title>Staff</title><link>https://blueyfest.dog/staff/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blueyfest.dog/staff/</guid><description>Staff Coordination Lycan - Con Chair Reiuiji - Vice Con Chair Events Simul - Lead Luck Rock - Music Lead A/V Larscis - Lead Reiuiji - Staff Gaming Leslie - Lead Tabletop Eliwood Sain - Lead Steel - Staff Design TechyCutie - Lead HauntedTuba - Staff Dawnfire - Bit Rate&amp;rsquo;s Mom Social Media Kevin - Lead Vendors Screw Loose - Lead VIP Relations Sirris - Lead Discord Fizzbuzz - Lead Midnight Aegis - Moderator Phosphorshy - Moderator PFC Rye of Shadows - Watcher King_CreepaLot - Watcher TheMostTopDog - Watcher Lord Midnight - Watcher Rarijack - Watcher Changelings Jamis - Staff Katharine - Staff Dexanth - Staff Charity Perrydotto - Lead Eurostream Jamis - Lead Special Thanks Twilight//RainbowDerpy - Streaming OPS, Resident Pony Town Expert Sleepy - PVFM Owner, Mentor Industrialice - PonyTown Project Lead Programmer PonyTown Team - For being supported for all these years Reiuiji - Our Resident Sylveon PonyTown Server Design Team Twilight//RainbowDerpy Cloudburst Delfynx Onyx Deadshot TheRealDashy</description></item><item><title>Vendors</title><link>https://blueyfest.dog/vendors/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blueyfest.dog/vendors/</guid><description>Vendors Haywaiian Horse Productions I Mele. I&amp;#39;m fueled by ponies, bacon and shiny bits! I sell a wide variety of MLP merch from stickers, buttons and prints, to charms, fluffy pillows, pins and much more!
Twitter&amp;#8203; Onix Angel Creations Hello I&amp;#39;m Onix! I&amp;#39;m a artist, content creator, and fursuit maker. I offer original works in my online store including pride clothing, lanyards, keychains, and more!
Instagram&amp;#8203;TikTok&amp;#8203;Twitch&amp;#8203;Twitter&amp;#8203; PlushTrapShop I’m a UK based seller who specialises in keychains, charms, stickers and prints.</description></item><item><title>What is Bluey?</title><link>https://blueyfest.dog/bluey/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blueyfest.dog/bluey/</guid><description>What is Bluey? Bluey is an Australian-animated television show for kids and adults that follows the adventures of a lovable Blue Heeler puppy named Bluey and her family. This includes her parents, Bandit and Chilli, and her younger sister, Bingo. The show takes place in the suburbs of Brisbane, Australia and focuses on everyday experiences and imaginative playtime activities that Bluey, her family, and her friends engage in. As they navigate the ups and downs of growing up and family life, the show explores their adventures together.</description></item><item><title>Who are the Mascots?</title><link>https://blueyfest.dog/mascots/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blueyfest.dog/mascots/</guid><description>Bit Rate Bit Rate is a high-energy and outgoing character who loves technology and video games. She is a young pup with a bright blue coat and a mischievous twinkle in her eye. Bit Rate is always eager to share her latest gadget or gaming strategy with her friends, often leading them on exciting adventures in the virtual world.
Despite her passion for technology, Bit Rate also values spending time with her friends and family.</description></item></channel></rss>